

Camilla Champion de Crespigny

Junior Software Engineer

0439 012 293 github.com/CamillaCdC camillachampiondecrespigny@gmail.com linkedin.com/in/camilla-champion-de-crespigny

ABOUT ME

I am a junior software engineer with a passion for creating well-tested, clean and easy to understand code that results in beautifully designed and intuitive user experiences. I enjoy working on projects that will have a positive impact upon people and the environment. I work best when I am being challenged and surrounded by a passionate team.

EDUCATION

2019 – 2020 General Assembly: Software Engineering Immersive Course

2016 – 2019
Swinburne University of Technology:
Bachelor of Business,
Major in Information
Systems, Co-Major in
Computer Science

June – July 2019 New Colombo Plan mobility project: FPT University Da Nang, Vietnam

2014
Monash University:
Year 1 Bachelor of
Medicine and Surgery

ADDITIONAL SKILLS

French lanaguge skills (B2 ILA level, Independent User)

EXPERIENCE

Dec 2019 - March 2020

SOFTWARE ENGINEERING IMMERSIVE COURSE • General Assembly

- HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Node.js, React, Ruby, Sinatra, Rails, OOP, Git & Git Hub, AJAX, APIs, Heroku, TDD, SQL & SQL Databases
- Full-stack app development, MVC and RESTful conventions
- Pair programming and group collaboration
- Project 1: Harry Potter tic-tac-toe JavaScript, HTML & CSS
- Project 2: CRUD App deployed on Heroku Ruby & SQL Database
- Project 3: Park-Inspector App Node.js & APIs
- Project 4: Portfolio Website React (deployed on Surge)

2018 - 2019

SUPPORT ANALYST • Marketplacer, marketplace platform provider

- Responded to clients questions, concerns and feature requests
- Used Zendesk, Jira, Trello platforms
- Created documentation on how to use the platform
- Reduced number of open support tickets from over 200 to under 50
- Created processes and rules for incoming support tickets
- Collaborated with developers and tested new features and bug fixes

2015 - 2018

OPERATIONS MANAGER • House of Home, online marketplace

- SEO specialist, blog formatting, and management of onsite advertising
- CRM/CMS management
- Customer service
- Created onsite advertising process

COMMUNITY SERVICE

2017 – present Blood Donor

2007 - present

Event General Assistant • Benalla Walk to D-Feet Motor Neurone Disease